newshipin.info 2016-11-01

# Privacy Policy - New Ship In

PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME AND CHANGES ARE EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES. NEW SHIP IN DOES NOT PROVIDE NOTICES OF CHANGES IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN BY POSTING THE CHANGES AT THIS WEB SITE.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO NEW SHIP IN OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEB SITES OWNED AND OPERATED BY NEW SHIP IN.

**1\. GENERAL PRIVACY TERMS**

New Ship In uses this website to operate a video reality service over the World Wide Web (the "Web").

Although some areas of this website may be viewed by members of the public, not all visitors to this website are users or members of the New Ship In community.

Publishers must be legal adults (of legal age to be legally able to enter into contracts in the jurisdiction in which they reside), corporations or other legal entities. Only persons or entities who apply for membership and are accepted by New Ship In are Publisher.

we do not have a generally applicable "privacy policy" that applies to all users of this website. Instead, our contracts contain terms that set forth the obligations of New Ship In with respect to the use and disclosure of the information that we gather from our members. In some cases, those terms may reflect negotiations that between New Ship In and other party; therefore, the terms are not necessarily the same for every individual member of our networks who uses this website.

##### **2\. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION BY New Ship In**

New Ship In is an owner of the information collected on this site. Information collected is in two distinct categories:  Member information and aggregated Web User information. This portion of New Ship In' privacy policy applies only to Publishers or Videos, not to general web users.

Members of New Ship In or related networks include publishers and advertisers involved in advertising transactions. Member information collected includes personally identifiable information that is necessary to conduct business, such as name, phone number, email address, social security number, and/or tax ID number. Payments made to and from New Ship In require the provision of and certain collection of personally identifiable information, which may include bank account information and credit card numbers. All information is collected, modified, and stored in a password protected environment. This information is used for the purposes of service, media delivery, contact, billing and accounts payable. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to non-New Ship In related entities and videos, unless and except as provided for herein. All information collection is explicit, voluntary, and manually entered by the Publisher, Video, Member or its agent.

**a. Identifiers and Cookies.**

A cookie is a small piece of information that is stored on a computer for the purpose of identifying that browser during interaction on websites. Cookies may be used to store items such as identifiers and user preferences. A website may set a cookie to the browser if the browser's preferences allow it. A browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has set, not those set by other websites.

When a consumer responds to or views an Internet advertisement served by New Ship In (such as through third-party Web sites or email solicitation) or visits the New Ship In site, a Cookie and/or gif file is sent to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the end user's Internet browser.

These Cookies provide New Ship In with information for the purpose of paying third-parties commissions when an Internet user clicks on a link, creates a lead, or makes a purchase on an advertiser's Web site. If the Internet user re-visits the advertiser's site directly, New Ship In may continue to track the user's activities (excluding PII) on the advertiser's site and reward the third-party Web site that referred the user. We may use Cookies to estimate the total reach of an advertising campaign, as well as to determine the frequency of display.

New Ship In may use cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

Access your information when you sign in so we can provide you with customized content.

Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using New Ship In.

Control the delivery of a series of advertisements to a web browser, and to limit the number of times a web browser receives any one advertisement. We also may use Internet browsing and online purchase data associated with an anonymous identifier to develop a predictive statistical user profile of the end user's needs and interests.

Optimize and personalize your experience and allow New Ship In to monitor log-ins and site traffic patterns. We record the IP address of members at each login, and this information is part of a secure database and is password protected.

We reserve the right to retain all ad delivery and reporting data as long as New Ship In finds it is reasonably necessary for accounting and audit purposes.

**b. Limitation on Liability.**

New Ship In expressly disclaims any obligation or liability to any user of any Video's website of any nature, including with regard to any data about that user that New Ship In obtains, processes, stores, uses or discloses.

**c. No Information Collected from Children.**

New Ship In **will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If** New Ship In **obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information,** New Ship In **has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties.** New Ship In **has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”).**

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to participate in and monitor their online activity.  If a parent or guardian believes that New Ship In has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us and we will use our best efforts to remove the information from our records.

##### **3\. SUBMISSIONS**

You agree that all content, comments, suggestions, ideas, complaints and other feedback relating to the New Ship In Service or Your Product that you disclose to us or post on the New Ship In Service or our users, may be used by us and our licensors, suppliers and licensees in any manner whatsoever, for any compensation and without limitation of any kind ("Submissions"). Notwithstanding the foregoing, we shall not be obligated to take action based upon any Submission provided by you.

Certain areas of the New Ship In Service may allow you to post Submissions that can be accessed and viewed by others, including the public in general. You may only post Submissions to public areas on the New Ship In Service that you created or that you have permission to post. In addition to all other restrictions set forth in this Agreement, you shall not post or transmit through the New Ship In Service any Submission, or otherwise engage in any conduct that:

\- is unlawful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, libelous, deceptive, fraudulent, invasive of another's privacy, tortious, or contains explicit or graphic descriptions, or accounts of, sexual acts; victimizes, harasses, degrades, or intimidates an individual or group of individuals on the basis of religion, gender, sexual orientation, race, ethnicity, age, or disability; or

\- impersonates any person, business or entity, including New Ship In and its employees and agents.

You understand and agree that by posting a Submission in any public area on the New Ship In Service, you also grant any third party permission to use and incorporate your ideas or comments without compensation or approval by you.

Your Data is not transmitted to third parties. However, New Ship In may release Data if the law requires it to do so or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant or to protect New Ship In’s rights and interests. It is New Ship In’s policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon receipt of a subpoena, and not produce your Data until approximately two weeks after receipt of the subpoena, so that you will have adequate opportunity to move to quash the subpoena in court.

New Ship In attaches great importance to the security of your Data, and takes all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

##### **4\. CONFIDENTIALITY**

Each Party acknowledges that Confidential Information (defined below) may be disclosed to the other Party during the course of this Agreement. The Receiving Party agrees that it will take reasonable steps, at least substantially equivalent to the steps it takes to protect its own proprietary information, during the term of this Agreement, and for a period of three (3) years following expiration or termination of this Agreement, to prevent the disclosure of the Disclosing Party’s Confidential Information, other than to its employees, videos, subsidiaries or other agents who must have access to such Confidential Information for the Recipient Party to perform its obligations or exercise its rights hereunder, who will each agree to comply with this section. As used herein, “Confidential Information” shall mean any information relating to or disclosed in the course of the Agreement, which is, or should be reasonably understood to be, confidential or proprietary to the Receiving Party, including, but not limited to, the material terms of this Agreement, sales, cost and other unpublished financial information, product and business plans, projections and marketing data. “Confidential Information” means all information disclosed by one party (the “Disclosing Party”) to the other party (the “Receiving Party”), whether in writing, orally, or in any other form, that is identified as confidential or proprietary or that, due to the nature of information or circumstances surrounding disclosure, should be treated as confidential or proprietary, including but not limited to software code, APIs, and technical documentation. “Confidential Information” shall not include information (a) already lawfully known to or independently developed by the Receiving Party, (b) disclosed in published materials, (c) generally known to the public, or (d) lawfully obtained from any third party.

##### **4\. ADVERTISING**

**6\. Some practical advice for young people**

If you are under 18, and you regularly use New Ship In, we ask you to carefully read the following information and advice.

-First, tell your parents if you create an account on New Ship In. It is important to have their agreement, and to explain to them how you plan on using the site (to send or share videos, create groups, etc.)

-Never give your personal information to other users.

**6A. parents:**

New Ship In provides all the tools necessary to ensure a safe experience for its users, particularly minors. On New Ship In, and on the Internet in general, it's important to be prudent just as it is in daily life.

We encourage parents to talk with their children about how they use New Ship In, especially concerning the videos they watch, and what they upload and share with others.

You are entitled to access and correct your Data by requesting to do so via the Contact us section, or by sending a letter to the following address: P.O. Box 451 Main Street Charlestown Nevis

##### **9\. NO DUTY TO MONITOR**

You agree that we are not liable for content that is provided by others on the New Ship In Service. We have no duty to pre-screen content, but we have the right to refuse to post or to edit submitted content. We reserve the right to remove content for any reason, but we are not responsible for any failure or delay in removing such material.
